Guide to the Pittsburgh Cultural Trust Records, 1975-2021 CTC.2000.02
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Benedum Center for the Performing Arts, 1983-1998; I.
  - Benedum Center performances - settlement files, 1987-1998; 2.
    - Midsummer Night's Dream and Sojourn, 1990-1991 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Trio and Unknown Territory and Square Dance, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Cats, 1990-1991 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - the Clancy Brothers, 1990-1991 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Rainbow Productions - Wicked Ways, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Die Fledermaus, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Placido Domingo, 1990-1991 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - the Barber of Seville, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Dances of the Czar and Sunset and the Mighty Casey, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Eugene Onegin, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - American Theater Arts for Youth Inc. - Wizard of Oz, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - True Value and WDSY-FM - the Grand Ole Opry American Tour, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Gladys Knight, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Feld Ballet, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Gene Kelly Awards, 1990-1991 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Heinz Hall - Starlight Express (cancelled), 1990-1991 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - American Theater Arts for Youth Inc. - Wizard of Oz, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Peter Pan, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Evita, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - A Little Night Music, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Heinz Hall - Jerome Robbins' Broadway, 1990-1991 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - No No Nanette, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Camelot, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Porgy & Bess, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Heinz Hall - Meet Me in St. Louis, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Miami City Ballet, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Ray Charles (cancelled), August 1991 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Rainbow Productions & OMP Inc. - One Monkey Don't Stop Now Show (cancelled), August 1991 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Heinz Hall Pace Theatrical Group - Bye Bye Birdie, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Romeo & Juliet, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - la Cenerentola, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Boris Godunov, 1991-1992 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - the Bolshoi, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Apollo and In the Glow of the Night and the River, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Buddy Holly (Box 36, Folder 3-4)
    - les Miserables, 1991-1992 (Box 36, Folder 5-7)
    - Heinz Hall - A Chorus Line, 1991-1992 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Diamond Bullet Corp - Come Out of the Rain (cancelled), 1991 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Maria & Luis of Sesame Street (cancelled), 1991-1992 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Coppelia, 1991-1992 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - H.J.D. Enterprises - Roots of Rock N Roll XIX, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - D.C.D. Entertainment - Keith Washington & Phyllis Hyman (cancelled), January 1992 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Kodo Drummers, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Private Lives, 1991-1992 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Cats, 1991-1992 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Man of the La Mancha, 1991-1992 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Rossini Variations and Return to the Strange Land and Theme and Variations, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Samson et Dalila, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Rigoletto, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Action Housing (cancelled), 1992 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Hunter's Moon and Fall River Legend and Great Galloping Gottschalk, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Latshaw Productions - the McGuire Sisters, 1991-1992 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Hubbard Street Dance Company, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - the Masked Ball, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - American Theater Arts for Youth Inc. - Wizard of Oz and Tom Sawyer, 1991-1992 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Heinz Hall - City of Angels, 1991-1992 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Gene Kelly Awards, 1991-1993 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - A.H. Inc. - Patti LaBelle, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Civic Light Opera pre-production week, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Heinz Hall - the Secret Garden, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Brigadoon, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Me and My Girl, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Jesus Christ Superstar, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 6-7)
    - Carousel, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Oliver, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Showboat, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - AIDS benefit, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Home Box Office and the Pittsburgh Film Office - Citizen Cohn, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - the Music of Andrew Lloyd Webber, 1992 (Box 40, Folder 1-2)
    - Pittsburgh Opera Optrans Test, 1992 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Lyon Opera Ballet, 1992 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Art Institute of Pittsburgh - student orientation, 1991-1992 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Heinz Hall - Aspects of Love, 1992-1993 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Taming of the Shrew, 1992 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Ballet Folklorico de Mexico, 1992 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Lascala (cancelled), 1991-1992 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Carmen, 1992-1993 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - K.D. Lang (cancelled), August 1992 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Ray Charles (cancelled), 1992 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - the Kingdom of the Shades from la Bayadere and the Prodigal Son and Configurations, 1992 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Tristan und Isolde, 1992-1993 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Morrissey (cancelled), 1992 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - the Gatlin Brothers Christmas Show, 1992 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - East Coast Pageants (cancelled), 1992 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - the Nutcracker, 1992-1993 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Heinz Hall - Once on this Island, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Tharp & Baryshnikov Cutting Up, 1992-1993 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Lettice & Lovage, 1992-1993 (Box 41, Folder 4-5)
    - Beauty Shop Part 2, 1992-1993 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Love Letters, 1992-1993 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Love Letters, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Don Quixote, 1992-1993 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Broadway Entertainment INC - Mannheim Steamroller, 1992-1993 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Mark Morris Dance Group, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - the Will Rogers Follies, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - David Copperfield, 1992-1993 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - H.J.D. Enterprises - Roots of Rock N Roll, 1992-1993 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Broadway Entertainment INC - Red Skelton, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Broadway Entertainment INC - Engelbert Humperdinck, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Alvin Ailey American Dance Theater, 1992-1993 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Serenade and Unknown Territory and Elite Syncopations, 1992-1993 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Heinz Hall - Camelot, 1992-1993 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - il trovatore, 1992-1993 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Concerto Barocco and Tarantella and the Mighty Casey, 1992-1993 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - American Jazz Awards (cancelled), 1992 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - American Theater Arts for Youth Inc. - Beauty and the Beast, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Black Ground Entertainment - Once in a Wife Time (cancelled), 1993 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - the Wilde Years, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Heinz Hall - Tommy Tune Tonight!, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Madama Butterfly, 1992-1993 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Civic Light Opera pre-production week, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Gene Kelly Awards, 1992-1993 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Fame, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Wizard of Oz, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - the Pirates of Penance, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Fiorello!, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - South Pacific, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Heinz Hall - Jesus Christ Superstar, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Phantom of the Opera gala benefit, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Phantom of the Opera, 1991-1993 (Box 44, Folder 5-6)
    - Sankai Juku, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Art Institute of Pittsburgh student orientation, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Don Giovanni, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Heinz Hall - My Fair Lady, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Cinderella, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Les Miserables, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Faust, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Tchaikovsky Festival, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Aurora's Wedding, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Crazy for You, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - the Nutcracker, 1993-1994 (Box 45, Folder 9-10)
    - Heinz Hall - Annie Get Your Gun, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Joffrey Ballet - Billboards, 1993-1994 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Lincoln Center Jazz Orchestra, 1993-1994 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Five Guys Named Moe, 1993-1994 (Box 46, Folder 4-5)
    - Cee-Jay Inc. - Bernie Mac in concert, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - H.J.D. Enterprises - Roots of Rock N Roll, 1993-1995 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - the Great Radio Music Hall Spectacular, 1993-1994 (Box 47, Folder 2-3)
    - Romeo and Juliet, 1993-1994 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Cats, 1993-1994 (Box 47, Folder 5-6)
    - Nikolais and Murray Louis Dance Company, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Hunter's Moon and Night Shadow and Great Galloping Gottschalk, 1993-1994 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Turandot, 1993-1994 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - the Who's Tommy, 1993-1994 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Rodeo and Who Cares Three Sisters, 1993-1994 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - la boheme, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - la Traviata 2000 finals, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Heinz Hall - Guys and Dolls, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - American Theater Arts for Youth Inc. - Wizard of Oz and Pinocchio, 1993-1994 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Maecenas X, 1993-1994 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Evita, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - the Andy Warhol Museum - Lou Reed Benefit concert (cancelled), 1994 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Three Rivers Young Peoples Orchestra - Twentieth Anniversary Spring Concert, 1993-1994 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Civic Light Opera pre-production week, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Gene Kelly Awards, 1993-1994 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Hot Mikado, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Music Man, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Music Man, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Seven Brides for Seven Brothers, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Fiddler on the Roof, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Mame, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 4-5)
    - Lunch, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Civic Light Opera season load out, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - New Scope Marketing - Isley Brothers, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Jack Purcell - a Salute to the Stanley Theatre for Spina bifida, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Merce Cunningham Dance Company, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Hello, Dolly!, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 6-7)
    - la Traviata, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Swan Lake, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Blood Brothers, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Bay Area Productions and Bill Graham - Jamie Foxx, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Broadway Entertainment - the Righteous Brothers, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - DiCesare-Engler Productions and Cee-Jay Inc. - Earth Wind & Fire, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - K. Barchetti Shops - a Halloween Fusical, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Master Entertainment Companies Inc. - Patti Austin, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Grease, 1994 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - le nozze di Figaro, 1994 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Firebird and Rubies and Petrouchka, 1994 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - the Nutcracker, 1994-1995 (Box 54, Folder 2-4)
    - Jelly's Last Jam, 1994-1995 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Benedum Center Live - First Night Pittsburgh, January 1995 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Dance Theatre of Harlem, 1994-1995 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Chicago Entertainment Inc. - Beauty Shop III, 1995 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Taming of the Shrew, 1994-1995 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - H.J.D. Enterprises - Roots of Rock N Roll, 1994-1995 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Tosca, 1994-1995 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - the Sound of Music, 1995 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - World Evangelism Inc. - Morris Cerullo, 1995 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Lucia Di Lammermoor, 1994-1995 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Elite Syncopations and Pas de trois Classique and the Mighty Casey, 1994-1995 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Angels in America, 1994-1995 (Box 57, Folder 1-2)
    - Jeff Clanagan and Bernard Gourley Productions - Def Comedy Jam, 1995 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Juvenile Diabetes Foundation - the Rainbow Gala, 1994-1995 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - a Midsummer Night's Dream, 1994-1995 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Heinz Hall - Joseph and the Amazing Technicolor Dreamcoat, 1995 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Maecenas XI, 1994-1995 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Gene Kelly Awards, 1994-1995 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Marnita Gibson and Derryck Tines - John P. Kee and the New Life Community Choir, 1995 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Renaissance City Choir - Tenth Anniversary Concert, 1995 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Still Here, 1995 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Civic Light Opera pre-production week, 1995 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - the Secret Garden, 1995 (Box 58, Folder 8-9)
    - Man of La Mancha, 1995 (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Man of La Mancha, 1995 (Box 59, Folder 1-2)
    - Cabaret, 1995 (Box 59, Folder 3-4)
    - the Most Happy Fella, 1995 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Singin' in the Rain, 1995 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Singin' in the Rain, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Godspell, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Buskers, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Buskers, 1995 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Dancer's Trust: Fourth Annual Benefit, September 1995 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - O Vertigo "Deluge", 1995-1996 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Kiss of the Spider Woman, 1995-1996 (Box 62, Folder 4-6)
    - Aida, 1995-1996 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Kaufmann's - Cinderella, 1995-1996 (Box 63, Folder 2-3)
    - Heinz Hall - Jekyll & Hyde, 1995 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Der Rosenkavalier, 1995-1996 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Marvelous Entertainment - Momma, I'm Sorry (cancelled), 1995 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Amazing Grace and the Ballad of You and Me and American Dream, 1995 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Orchard Hill Production Team - Orchard Hill Church, 1994-1996 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - the Boys Choir of Harlem, 1995-1996 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - the Nutcracker, 1994-1996 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - the Nutcracker, December 1995 (Box 65, Folder 1-2)
    - Benedum Center Live - First Night Pittsburgh, 1995-1996 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Mark Morris Dance Group, 1995-1996 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - DiCesare-Engler Productions - Shining Time Station, 1995-1996 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Heinz Hall - Ain't Misbehavin', 1995-1996 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Giselle and XII Men, 1996 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Heinz Hall - Cats, February 1996 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - PNC dinner on Benedum stage, 1996 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Alvin Ailey American Dance Theater, 1995-1996 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Ty Johnson Special Events / Rome Records - Immature in concert, 1996 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Chirp Promotions and Entertainment Inc. - Bernie Mac in concert, 1995-1996 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - H.J.D. Enterprises - Roots of Rock N Roll, 1995-1996 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Cosi fan tutte, 1995-1996 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Billy the Kid and the Four Temperaments and Return to the Strange Land, 1995-1996 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - the Magic of David Copperfield, 1996 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Heinz Hall - Carousel, 1995-1996 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Cavalleria rusticana and I Pagliacci, 1995-1996 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - the Great Gatsby, 1995-1996 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Joe, 1995-1996 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - les Miserables, 1995-1996 (Box 69, Folder 1-2)
    - Damn Yankees, 1995-1996 (Box 70, Folder 1-2)
    - Gene Kelly Awards, 1995-1996 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - DiCesare-Engler Inc. - Tori Amos, 1996 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - the Desert Song, 1995-1996 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Annie, 1996 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Annie, June 1996 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Into the Woods, 1996 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - My Fair Lady, 1996 (Box 71, Folder 3-4)
    - 42nd Street, 1996 (Box 72, Folder 1-2)
    - 1776, 1996 (Box 72, Folder 3-4)
    - Down Lo Promotions Inc. - Comedy Explosion, 1996 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - McDonald's Hip-Hop Comedy Jam, 1996 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Cultural Trust benefit gala featuring Bobby Short, 1996 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Haymon Entertainment Inc. - Isley Brothers, 1996 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - DiCesare-Engler - Bruce Springsteen, 1996 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Civic Light Opera 50th anniversary gala, 1995-1996 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Heinz Hall - Funny Girl, 1996 (Box 73, Folder 6-7)
    - Maceba Affairs - Whatever Happened to Black Love, 1996 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Mefistofele, 1996 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Sleeping Beauty, 1996-1997 (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Sleeping Beauty, 1996 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Chamber Theater Productions Inc. - Tour de Force, 1996 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Sankai Juku, 1996-1997 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - DiCesare-Engler - Peter Paul & Mary, 1995-1996 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Barber of Seville, 1996-1997 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Smokey Joe's Cafe, 1996 (Box 74, Folder 6-7)
    - Grease, 1995-1996 (Box 75, Folder 1-2)
    - Nutcracker, 1996-1997 (Box 75, Folder 3-5)
    - Benedum Center Live - First Night in Pittsburgh, 1996-1997 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Metro Real Estate Services - Smothers Brothers corporate presentation, 1996-1997 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - DiCesare-Engler - Jazz Explosion, 1996-1997 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - A.L.W. Entertainment Inc. - Kirk Franklin, 1996-1997 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Romeo and Juliet, 1996-1997 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Stage One Productions Inc. - Ray Scott (cancelled), 1996-1997 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - the Magic Flute, 1996-1997 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - H.J.D. Enterprises - Roots of Rock N Roll, 1996-1997 (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Concerto Barocco and Tabula Rasa and Harvest Moon, 1997 (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Heinz Hall - Deathtrap, 1997 (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Maecenas dinner XIII, 1995-1997 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Jewels, 1997 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - American Theater Arts for Youth Inc. - Cinderella, 1997 (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Chamber Theater Productions Inc. - Encore, 1996-1997 (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - American Theater Arts for Youth Inc. - Wind in the Willows, 1997 (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Philadanco, 1996-1997 (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Don Carlo, 1996-1997 (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Chris Rock (cancelled), April 1997 (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - How to Succeed in Business Without Really Trying, 1996-1997 (Box 78, Folder 9-10)
    - Rivers of Desire and Ballad of You and Me and Symphony in C, 1997 (Box 78, Folder 11)
    - Gene Kelly Awards, 1996-1997 (Box 78, Folder 12)
    - Civic Light Opera pre-production week, 1997 (Box 78, Folder 13)
    - Chirp Promotions - Cedric the Entertainer, 1997 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Heinz Hall - a Chorus Line, 1996-1997 (Box 79, Folder 2-3)
    - Cinderella, 1997 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - la Cage Aux Follies, 1997 (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Kiss Me Kate, 1997 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Chess, 1997 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Gypsy, 1997 (Box 80, Folder 3-4)
    - Heinz Hall and PACE Theatrical Group Inc. - Stomp, 1996-1997 (Box 80, Folder 5-6)
    - Miss Saigon, 1997 (Box 81, Folder 1-7)
    - Miss Saigon, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 1-5)
    - Miss Saigon, 1997 (Box 83, Folder 1-3)
    - Miss Saigon, 1994-1997 (Box 84, Folder 1-3)
    - AFL-CIO - Billy Bragg, 1997-1998 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - les Enfants Terribles, 1997 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Dracula, 1997 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - Housing Authority of the City of Pittsburgh - Jeffrey Osbourne, 1997 (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - Bye Bye Charlie and Charlie Gray Dinner, 1997 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - Norma, 1997 (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - DiCesare-Engler Inc. - En Vogue, 1997 (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - the King and I, 1997-1998 (Box 85, Folder 8-10)
    - Les Brown Enterprises Inc. - Developing Greatness with Les Brown, 1997 (Box 85, Folder 11)
    - Master Class, 1997-1998 (Box 86, Folder 1-3)
    - Carmen, 1997-1998 (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - Western Symphony and American Dream and Liberty Bell Pas de Deux and Who Cares?, 1997-1998 (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - Big, 1997-1998 (Box 86, Folder 6-8)
    - the Nutcracker, 1996-1998 (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Benedum Center Live - First Night Pittsburgh, 1997-1998 (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Metro Real Estate Services corporate presentation, 1997-1998 (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Chicago, 1997-1998 (Box 87, Folder 4-6)
    - Chicago, 1997-1998 (Box 88, Folder 1-2)
    - Harlem Nutcracker, 1997-1998 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Coppelia, 1998 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - H.J.D. Enterprises - Roots of Rock N Roll, 1997-1998 (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - Poppe Tyson Inc - the Addy's Awards presentation, 1997-1998 (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - Sears - Walt "Baby" Love's Power '98, 1998 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - American Indian Dance Company, 1997-1998 (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - Romeo et Juliette, 1997-1998 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - Scotch Symphony and Unknown Territory and Ballet Imperial, 1997-1998 (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - les Miserables, 1997-1999 (Box 89, Folder 5-7)
    - les Miserables, April 1998 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Madama Butterfly, 1997-1998 (Box 90, Folder 2-3)
    - Chirp Promotions - Bernie Mac, 1998 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Chamber Theater Productions Inc. - Encore, 1997-1998 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - P & P Consulting Inc. - I Know I've Been Changed, 1998 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Pittsburgh Dance Council production (cancelled), 1997-1998 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Maecenas dinner XIV, 1997-1998 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Don Quixote, 1997-1998 (Box 91, Folder 6-7)
    - National Trust for Historic Preservation conference, 1997-1999 (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Gene Kelly Awards, 1994-1998 (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - Keith Farris comedy show, 1998 (Box 91, Folder 10)
    - Heinz Hall - Rent, 1997-1998 (Box 92, Folder 1-5)
    - Peter Pan, 1998 (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - Peter Pan, 1998 (Box 93, Folder 1-3)
    - Civic Light Opera pre-production week, 1997-1998 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Joseph and the Amazing Technicolor Dreamcoat, 1998 (Box 93, Folder 5-9)
    - Gigi, 1998 (Box 94, Folder 1-2)
    - Camelot, 1998 (Box 94, Folder 3-4)
    - Phantom, 1998 (Box 94, Folder 5-6)
    - On the Town, 1998 (Box 94, Folder 7-8)
    - Wheel of Fortune, 1998 (Box 95, Folder 1-4)
    - Show Boat, 1997-1998 (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Show Boat, 1998 (Box 96, Folder 1-4)
    - Show Boat, September 1998 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Rainbow Inc. - Ain't No Woman Like the One I Got, 1998 (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - Rainbow Inc. - the Hit Men of Comedy Show, 1995-1998 (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Pittsburgh International Children's Theater - Circo Zoppe' Europa, 1998 (Box 97, Folder 4-5)
    - DiCesare Entertainment - Saints Aint's & Wannabes, 1998 (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - Trisha Brown Company, October 1998 (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - Andrea Chenier, 1998 (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - Heinz Hall - Victor / Victoria, 1998-1999 (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - Heinz Hall - Victor / Victoria, 1998 (Box 98, Folder 1-2)
    - Swan Lake, 1998 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Bill Graham Presents - the Big Comfy Couch, 1998 (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - I.A.G. Theater Group Inc. - Why Good Girls Like Bad Boys, 1998 (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - L'Elisir D'Amore, 1998 (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Sunset Boulevard, 1998 (Box 98, Folder 7-8)
    - Sunset Boulevard, 1998-1999 (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - the Nutcracker, 1998-1999 (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - First Night Pittsburgh Inc. - First Night Pittsburgh 1999, 1998-1999 (Box 99, Folder 3-4)
- District Development, 1979-2000; II.
  This series consists of office files and architectural materials related to the Penn-Liberty Historic District of downtown Pittsburgh. This area, also known as Pittsburgh's Cultural District, was named to the US Register of Historic Districts in 1987. Primarily contains records on the development and planning of the O'Reilly Theater, the Allegheny Riverfront park, and Theater Square.
  - District Development files, 1979-2000; 1.